<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260515170000 +0000" stop="20260515180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Lobo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mountain man Luke Brazo joins Matt in a hunt for a vicious wolf terrorizing the area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260515180000 +0000" stop="20260515190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Dark Past</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>The men of the Ponderosa cannot understand why bounty hunter Dev Farnum (Dennis Hopper) is so unfriendly and secretive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260515190000 +0000" stop="20260515193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Jailbird</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>When Lucas hires an ex-con as a ranch hand, the man is the first one under suspicion when a robbery and murder occur in the area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260515193000 +0000" stop="20260515200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Meeting At Midnight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas helps his former Army captain, now an undercover federal agent, infiltrate a gang of bank robbers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260515200000 +0000" stop="20260515210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Alexander Portlass Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Kidnapped, Flint is forced to scout and find a lost Aztec treasure. As some of the men were previously thrown off the wagon train, their unfriendliness is certain unless he can help them find the lost treasure of Montezuma.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260515210000 +0000" stop="20260515220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Show Biz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A photo shoot at the station gets John excited. A country doctor helps Roy and John when they can't reach Rampart on a call. The paramedics rescue a man drowning in a swimming pool and two stuntmen trapped on a waterfall at a movie studio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260515220000 +0000" stop="20260515223000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Chitterly's Lover: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hogan becomes convinced that Crittendon can't fool Hitler, things get complicated when Chitterly escapes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260515223000 +0000" stop="20260515230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>38 Across</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Befuddled by a crossword puzzle, Hawkeye persuades his old friend, Tippy Brooks, a whiz at puzzles, to come to camp. Tippy arrives with his commanding officer, Admiral Prescot, thinking it's a medical emergency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260515230000 +0000" stop="20260515233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ping Pong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Colonel Harold Beckett lies wounded in post-op waiting to get back to the front for five more days of combat duty to get his promotion. Meanwhile, Cho Lin, the Ping Pong champ, is engaged to Soony. He leaves to get her a ring, when the South Korean army conscripts him. He arrives at the 4077th as a wounded soldier, and after being patched up he is married at the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260515233000 +0000" stop="20260516000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>End Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Billy Tyler, a young black sergeant, is brought into camp with a bullet wound in the leg. He is a football player, and when he discovers that his leg has been amputated, he wants to die. After talks with Radar, Billy agrees that he must live on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516000000 +0000" stop="20260516003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Physical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney learns that in order to pass the mandatory physical for the deputy's office, he must weigh more and be taller. Andy and Aunt Bee try to stretch him and fatten him up, until Andy comes up with the solution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516003000 +0000" stop="20260516010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Lawman Barney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's ability to be a lawman is put to the test with some peddlers and he fails. His confidence is shattered until Andy steps in behind the scenes and warns the peddlers of "Fife the Fierce."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516010000 +0000" stop="20260516013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>She's The One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray sees Robert's date do something really strange.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516013000 +0000" stop="20260516020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Marie's Vision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra suggests Marie visit an eye doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516020000 +0000" stop="20260516023000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>All Bets Off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Dorothy's gambling problem resurfaces after a visit to the race track.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516023000 +0000" stop="20260516030000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Blanche Delivers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Blanche's daughter wants to give birth in a birthing center.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516030000 +0000" stop="20260516033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Steve Lawrence, Tim Conway, And Maggie Smith</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Stake Out, Carol's police stakeout turns into a blind date. Then, in A Visit from Karen, a star-struck Carol badgers an old friend about her experiences as a Hollywood starlet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516033000 +0000" stop="20260516043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Angry Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Willard Nesbitt faked his drowning death in a boating accident so his wife could collect the double indemnity life insurance money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516043500 +0000" stop="20260516050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A World Of Difference</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman discovers that life as he knows it doesn't really exist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516050500 +0000" stop="20260516053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Festive Season</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A man believes that his sister murdered his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516053500 +0000" stop="20260516060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Listen, Listen</sub-title>
    <desc>"Three women have been strangled. Police arrest a stocking salesman as the killer. Mr. Morgan knows who the real culprit is: he has seen the next murder in a dream. He tries to tell people, but no one listens. His wife ignores him as well, which is unfortunate because she is the strangler's next victim."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516060500 +0000" stop="20260516070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Sound Of Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is in search of a businessman who disappeared without a trace. Then a second disappearance happens, and this time the culprit leaves a tape recorder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516070500 +0000" stop="20260516080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Flight Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A political refugee gets a unwilling helping hand from Frank when he creates a change of identity to help flee the country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516080500 +0000" stop="20260516090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Target Of A Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>An heiress doesn't know that the fortune hunter she's fallen for has murdered her benefactor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516090000 +0000" stop="20260516093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Look Me Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Billie Jo becomes jealous of her sweetheart, aviator Steve Elliott, and her youngest sister, Betty Jo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516093000 +0000" stop="20260516100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>That's Max???</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Billie Jo is stunned when Steve Elliott all but announces that he is about to marry a former girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516100000 +0000" stop="20260516103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Drysdale's Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale's father comes to Beverly Hills to visit. When he learns of the Clampetts, he decides he wants to meet them. He visits and ends up playing poker and pool with Jed. But Farquhar loses all his money because his tricks backfire and the Clampetts are better at the games then he could even imagine. In the end, Jed suggests they give up the gambling and just play a friendly game of pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516103000 +0000" stop="20260516110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Farquhar Stays On</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny has taken interest in Mrs. Drysdale’s father, Mr. Farquhar. And Farquhar is trying to get someone to go to Las Vegas with him, first asking Drysdale, who turns him down. He asks Granny to accompany him, and Granny believes this is a marriage proposal. Farquhar tells Drysdale about this, who is against it, and Drysdale tells Jed, who is all for it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516110000 +0000" stop="20260516113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Olive’s Sweepstake Ticket, Insect To Injury, Stealin Aint Honest, Nearlyweds</sub-title>
    <desc>"Olive wins a sweepstakes and causes Popeye trouble when a gust of wind blows the winning ticket out of her hand., Popeye's new house is attacked by termites., Popeye and Olive Oyl sail off to find the whereabouts of Olive's gold mine., Popeye and Bluto both plan to marry Olive Oyl."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516113000 +0000" stop="20260516120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Love That Pup, Little Mole, Blue Cat Blues</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom accidentally grabs Tyke, Spike the bulldog's son, when he is trying to get to Jerry., A mole uses two bottle bottoms for lenses and sees the world in a brand new way which proves difficult for him., Jerry narrates the rough times Tom is going through as he loses his girlfriend to his rival Butch."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516120000 +0000" stop="20260516130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Everglade Raid, The Case Of The Elephant's Trunk, Lotsa Luck, Foot Brawl, Born To Peck, Candyland, Big Bite</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody heads down to the Everglades to hunt alligators so he can sell them to be made into suitcases. When he get there, he meets an alligator that wants to eat him., Inspector Willoughby tracks a rajah's kidnapped elephant., Woody and Sugarfoot have terrible luck, which doesn't get better when he finds a four-leaf clover., Charlie tries unsuccessfully to convince his son he was a football star in college., A tired and elderly Woody reminices on his childhood with his father. Despondent, he attempts to commit suicide, only to be thwarted by the cartoonist., The Sandman takes a boy and his puppy to Candyland., Woody rescues his dog Duffy from a bully dogcatcher."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516130000 +0000" stop="20260516140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Carrotblanca, Hopalong Casualty, Mouse Wreckers, Bonanza Bunny, Naughty Neighbors, The Jet Cage, Hare-breadth Hurry</sub-title>
    <desc>"A parody of Casablanca. , The coyote thinks he got the Road Runner by the neck but it turns out to be just a cloud in the shape of his neck. , Hubie and Bertie are determined to live in the house that Claude Cat lives in. , Bugs joins an 1896 gold town and duels a French-Canadian version of Yosemite Sam. , Porky Pig attempts to halt an ancient feud between two families. , Granny orders a new-fangled flying bird cage for Tweety, jet-powered and complete with crash helmet. Tweety tries it out in the backyard and heckles Sylvester. , The Coyote chases a speeding cloud that turns out to be Bugs Bunny! "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516140000 +0000" stop="20260516150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Infernal Machine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A federal judge is threatened by a bomb-throwing clockmaker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516150000 +0000" stop="20260516160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Christine Elliot Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Her father on his deathbed, Christine Elliot decides to fulfill his dream of a boys school and joins the wagon train. However, one man is determined to stop her unless he collects his pound of flesh.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516160000 +0000" stop="20260516170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Days Of Wrath</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Jarrod seeks to avenge the death of his new wife at the hands of a man he sent to prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516170000 +0000" stop="20260516180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Johnny Cross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly intervenes when two bounty hunters try to kill a desperado who claims he's innocent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516180000 +0000" stop="20260516190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Pressure Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura Dayton's Aunt Lil comes to visit and quickly decides it's time she help the hesitant Adam propose to her favorite niece. Her plan is to make Adam jealous by using his cousin, Will, but it doesn't go exactly as planned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516190000 +0000" stop="20260516193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Nora</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas finds himself involved in murder when he gallantly steps to the aid of a beautiful woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516193000 +0000" stop="20260516200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hangman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-convict is blamed for a brutal crime despite his claims of rehabilitation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516200000 +0000" stop="20260516210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Ten Trees</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The drovers find a young white woman dressed as an indian, babbling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516210000 +0000" stop="20260516213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Juliet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Juliet Harper is being hunted by the grandsons of Colonel Jeremiah Pike. Paladin meets her on the stage and now the Colonel is after both of them, and Paladin is without a gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516213000 +0000" stop="20260516220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Baa-baa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh is hired to find Baa-Baa, a beloved pet of Mrs. Goode's. Her husband is desperate to find Baa-Baa as he is in the dog house with her until Baa-Baa returns. Josh reluctantly goes to look for the lost sheep amid much ridicule from other ranchers and cowboys alike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260516220000 +0000" stop="20260517000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Punch Drunks, Three Little Beers, What's The Matador, Three Little Twirps, Gents Without Cents, Half Shot Shooters</sub-title>
    <desc>"Moe is a boxing promoter looking for a good fighter.  , The Stooges are inept deliverymen at a brewery.   , The Stooges are discharged from the army after WW I, and promptly administer some revenge to their mean sergeant.  , The Stooges are actors traveling to perform at a fiesta in Mexico.  After they accidentally switch suitcases with that of Dolores, a lovely senorita they met on trip down, they must sneak into her house to retrieve their suitcase.  When they are confronted by her jealous husband he vows to kill them if he sees them again.  At the fiesta where they are performing a comedy bullfight (Curly is the matador, Moe and Larry are in a bull costume) the husband bribes the attendants to let a real bull into the ring.  Curly knocks the bull out with a head butt and becomes a hero. , The Stooges get a job putting up posters for a circus but discover that instead of money, their pay is tickets to the show.  When trying to scalp their tickets gets them in trouble, they hide out backstage where Curly has an encounter with a bearded lady and Moe and Larry hide in a horse suit.  When they're caught, the circus manager gives them a choice of going to jail or joining the circus.  What they don't know is that they are to be targets for the Zulu spear thrower.  When Curly hits the spear thrower with one of his own spears, the boys are on the run once again. , The Stooges are three small time actors looking for a job.  They meet three girl dancers in the situation and get a small part in a big producers show at the shipyard.  When the rest of the cast doesn't show up, the Stooges and the girls must put on the whole show themselves.  The show is a hit and the Stooges marry the girls and head to Niagara Falls for their honeymoon. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517000000 +0000" stop="20260517023000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Rosemary's Baby</sub-title>
    <desc>"A young couple move into an apartment, only to be surrounded by peculiar neighbors and occurrences. When the wife becomes mysteriously pregnant, paranoia over the safety of her unborn child begins to control her life."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517023000 +0000" stop="20260517030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Batman's Anniversary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E45</episode-num>
    <desc>During a surprise anniversary party for the Dynamic Duo and the Gotham Police, the Riddler uses a ruse to steal a golden calf filled with charity money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517030000 +0000" stop="20260517040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Journey To Babel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Spock meets his estranged father when the Enterprise escorts a group of ambassadors to a conference on the planet Babel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517040000 +0000" stop="20260517043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Czar Of The Underworld</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Clark and Inspector Henderson are warned by a gang leader to "lay off" of a film about crime. After murder and sabotage on the set, Superman sees that the film is completed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517043000 +0000" stop="20260517050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost Wolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Lumberjacks leave their job, fearing a werewolf. A forest fire enlivens the plot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517050000 +0000" stop="20260517060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Space Vikings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A storm looms and the two gloves of Thor appear from space and fly straight into the waiting hands of Dr. Smith. They are then taken away by the real Thor, who will decide their fate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517060000 +0000" stop="20260517070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Nelson and the Seaview crew battle a saboteur spy and a mystery sub that tries to destroy them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517070000 +0000" stop="20260517080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>On A Clear Night, You Can See Earth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A giant scientist develops a pair of infra-red goggles which lets him easily track the Earthlings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517080000 +0000" stop="20260517090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost Of Nero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1915, the travelers try to keep the ghost of Nero from taking revenge on a descendant of Nero's rival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517090000 +0000" stop="20260517100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Enemy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman discovers an injured alien.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517100000 +0000" stop="20260517110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Dam</sub-title>
    <desc>"A beaver colony dams up the river in Adams' valley, placing his cabin and surrounding wildlife at risk. Should Adams take Mad Jack's advice and destroy the dam and run out the beavers - or is there a more humane solution?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517110000 +0000" stop="20260517113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Spotted Ghost Of The Desert Part I</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the Kalahari region of southern Africa, Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler study the life and habits of the graceful and cunning leopard by establishing a camp near a hidden leopard den."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517113000 +0000" stop="20260517120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Spotted Ghost Of The Desert Part Ii</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim continue their investigation into the home life of the leopard."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517120000 +0000" stop="20260517123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Against The Clock</sub-title>
    <desc>"Man loves speed and this episode answers some of the most pertinent inquiries as to what animals hold the records."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517123000 +0000" stop="20260517130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Sahara South</sub-title>
    <desc>"A horseback safari into the wilds of Rhodesia where Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler explore the vast grasslands, rivers and forests and observe an amazing variety of rare animals.  In this episode, the forming waters swirl around tons of struggling hippo in a dangerous project to tranquilize and capture one of the largest members of the wild kingdom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517130000 +0000" stop="20260517133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Miracle Of Motion</sub-title>
    <desc>"Oddities of animal motion include mammals that fly, birds that climb with their shoulders, lizards that dive and snakes that travel sideways."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517133000 +0000" stop="20260517140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Valley Of Eagles</sub-title>
    <desc>"A valley in the mountain country of the western United States is the territory of the Golden Eagle, America’s largest and most powerful bird of prey.  Marlin and Jim locate an eyrie (nest) of this magnificent bird, and build a blind high on a rocky cliff so they can photograph its nesting habits. Humor and drama are interwoven as the young eagle, in his search for food, follows a skunk into his den…and later finds out that a fast dive at a sitting duck results in his first unwanted bath.  His territory is invaded by a forest fire, and the hunting is made easier as the other animals of the valley flee the flames.  He is trapped by man in a scientific experiment, but later released to continue his life in the “Valley of Eagles.”"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517140000 +0000" stop="20260517143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Alice, Hello</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The kids begin to give Alice the cold shoulder treatment after she reveals that Greg and Peter broke an antique lamp of Carol's. The girls join the bandwagon when Alice innocently tells Carol that Marcia left the stereo on all night. Feeling unwanted and no longer needed, Alice quits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517143000 +0000" stop="20260517150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Greg's Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg is crazy for his latest girlfriend, Jennifer. Things get difficult when he learns that both Jennifer and Marcia are competing for head cheerleader -- and he just happens to be one of the judges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517150000 +0000" stop="20260517153000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Military School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro finally decides on his life’s calling again. He decides on being a five-star general. Jethro is hoping to attend West Point, but Drysdale talks him into going to Haven Hurst. Granny is against him joining because he might get hurt, and Drysdale is having trouble getting him in because this military academy is for boys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517153000 +0000" stop="20260517160000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Common Cold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is looking to cure people and learns of Mr. Drysdale’s illness. He has a common cold. Granny says that she has the ability to cure it with one spoonful of “cold cure.” She makes her cold cure to share with Dr. Clyburn, but he turns her down and mean-mouths her. So she decides to start her own doctor’s office and use her cold cure to treat folks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517160000 +0000" stop="20260517163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a stranger comes to town, Barney and the people of Mayberry grow suspicious when he seems to know too much about them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517163000 +0000" stop="20260517170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Gets In Pictures</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy finally gets her shot at Hollywood stardom—as a chorus girl photographed in a lavish musical. But she had better not get a swelled head, because the headdress she has to wear is too big as it is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517170000 +0000" stop="20260517173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Freckles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Clarence gets fed up with Beaver calling him Lumpy, he gives Beaver a new nickname, Freckles. This leads Beaver to become self-conscious about his freckles and takes steps to try to remove them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517173000 +0000" stop="20260517180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Won't Eat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is determined not to eat brussels sprouts and adamantly refuses to eat them when June serves them for dinner. In order to go to a football game, Ward makes Beaver promise that he will eat brussels sprouts the next time they are served. Beaver quickly finds himself confronted with the "deadly" vegetables when the Cleavers go out to eat at a posh restaurant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517180000 +0000" stop="20260517190000 +0000">
    <title>Charlie's Angels</title>
    <sub-title>Terror On Ward One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Kelly and Jill play nurse as as the Angels try to snare a rapist who's been preying on student nurses at a local hospital. As usual, there's no shortage of suspects, including a pill-popping chief surgeon, a lovesick intern and a cantankerous old man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517190000 +0000" stop="20260517200000 +0000">
    <title>Hart to Hart</title>
    <sub-title>Sixth Sense</sub-title>
    <desc>"A young woman's clairvoyance uncovers the murder of a twin sister she never knew."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517200000 +0000" stop="20260517210000 +0000">
    <title>Fantasy Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Best Seller / Tomb</sub-title>
    <desc>"An archeologist and his daughter confront an Egyptian curse on Fantasy Island. A young man desires the limelight awarded a best-selling author on Fantasy Island."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517210000 +0000" stop="20260517220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Groupies / Audition / Doc's Nephew</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Doc's nephew is making a move on his girlfriend. A psychiatrist, who is on vacation is followed by four of his patients. An actor pursues the writer of a soap opera, who rejected for a role on her show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517220000 +0000" stop="20260517223000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Once, In St. Olaf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Rose makes a stunning discovery while admitting a patient at the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517223000 +0000" stop="20260517230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Patrick Mediate- Movie Props &amp; Costumes</sub-title>
    <desc>"Movie buff Patrick Mediate put his time in pandemic lockdown to good use; cut off from friends and family, he began filling his house with his favorite movie characters, in the form of iconic screen-used props and costumes. Now Patrick introduces Lisa to his collection of instantly recognizable figures, including Elvira, through a gown from "Mistress of the Dark," Whoopi Goldberg, thanks to a habit from "Sister Act 2," Daisy Ridely, courtesy of Rey's staff from "Star Wars: The Force Awakens," and a range of character pieces, including Robin Williams' shirt, from Steven Spielberg's "Hook." Lisa's brought along movie-props authority Dan Gastin to both appraise Patrick's collection, then to try and tempt him into a trade for one of its choicest items. And fair warning: Dan's more than ready to keep going to the mat for what he's after!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517230000 +0000" stop="20260517233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hanky Panky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Nurse Carrie Donovan receives a Dear Jane letter from her husband, and practically falls apart. B.J. consoles her, and they spend the night together. Feelings of guilt come over B.J. until he discusses them with Donovan and the air is cleared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260517233000 +0000" stop="20260518000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hepatitis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy comes down with infectious hepatitis, and Hawkeye has to give the whole camp antibiotics, while dealing with a psychosomatic back pain. Meanwhile, B.J. has to perform a very difficult operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518000000 +0000" stop="20260518003000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>If At Last You Don't Succeed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Stan has finally hit it big with a new invention.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518003000 +0000" stop="20260518010000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Snap Out Of It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Dorothy decides to help Sophia with the Meals on Wheels program.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518010000 +0000" stop="20260518013000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Wham, Bam, Thank You Mammy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Blanche gets an unexpected visit from her childhood "mammy" (nanny).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518013000 +0000" stop="20260518020000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Feelings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Dorothy receives threats after failing a football star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518020000 +0000" stop="20260518023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Thought That Counts, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray frantically tries to figure out what to get Debra for Christmas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518023000 +0000" stop="20260518030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Grandpa Steals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank must find a way to fix his image with Ally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518030000 +0000" stop="20260518033000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Election Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A local election has the Bunker family in turmoil as Mike and Gloria are all for Claire Packer, a woman, which is exactly why Archie is dead set against her. However, once down at the voting booths, Archie soon realizes that he can't vote because he isn't registered, leaving it up to him to try to convince Edith to vote for his candidate of choice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518033000 +0000" stop="20260518040000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Blockbuster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunkers are having problems with their furnace which gets Archie entertaining the idea of possibly moving to California. When an unscrupulous black real-estate salesman, Mr. Byrd, offers Archie a hefty sum of money for his home, Archie is all for it despite Mike's warnings that Byrd is a blockbuster (someone who persuades white home-owners to sell by appealing to the fear that minority groups will move into the neighborhood causing property values to decline).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518040000 +0000" stop="20260518043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>When A Bowling Pin Talks, Listen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob writes a sketch, only to discover another comedy show did almost the exact same thing!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518043000 +0000" stop="20260518050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>That's My Boy???</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob and Laura think they brought the wrong baby home from the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518050000 +0000" stop="20260518053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Something Fishy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Norton don't want to take their wives on a Raccoon fishing trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518053000 +0000" stop="20260518060000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>On Stage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, Alice and Ed are in a Raccoon play, and Ralph expects to be a big star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518060000 +0000" stop="20260518070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Ultimatum</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The IMF has 16 hours to find a nuclear bomb placed by an extortionist, Dr. Cooper, in one of seven Pacific Coast cities and his associates, who can disarm the bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518070000 +0000" stop="20260518080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>A Clean And Quiet Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble makes the mistake of going to Clark City, a corrupt gambling town. Fred Johnson (the one-armed man) is there as well, and has two corrupt cops beat up Kimble. When Richard survives the attack, Johnson then puts out a contract on him. Kimble eventua</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518080000 +0000" stop="20260518090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>The Acolyte</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell follows a murder trail that leads him to a religious sect and a plot to defraud a mentally disturbed woman."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518090000 +0000" stop="20260518093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Personnel - The Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The problems of policemen's wives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518093000 +0000" stop="20260518100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - The Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The police go after a college student who has turned to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518100000 +0000" stop="20260518103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 92 -- Tell Him He Pushed Back A Little Too Hard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed respond to repeated calls about an argument between two men and their wives over a boat they co-own. The feud escalates and ends with a fatal conclusion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518103000 +0000" stop="20260518110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 22: So This Little Guy Goes Into This Bar, And...</sub-title>
    <desc>"A fur burglary, a family fight and a loud party."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518110000 +0000" stop="20260518120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' Switzerland</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit Switzerland on the latest stop of their Trekkin the Globe tour."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518120000 +0000" stop="20260518123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Big Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Constantly entering contests, Beaver's latest one has him selling raffle tickets in hopes of winning a prize. Surprisingly, he does indeed win third prize and the prize is a $3,500 sports car. However, his dreams are dashed when Eddie's premonition comes true, Ward breaks the news that Beaver can't keep the car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518123000 +0000" stop="20260518130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally The Lifeguard</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally is all set to begin his job as a lifeguard but is let down when he learns that had been a mistake and he's not old enough to fill the position, so instead he is hired to sell candy and hot dogs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518130000 +0000" stop="20260518140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Careless Kidnapper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E27</episode-num>
    <desc>After a fake kidnaping goes wrong, Dr. Gregory Pelham finds that his secret experiments in rehabilitating prominent alcoholics have resulted in a mess of blackmail and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518140000 +0000" stop="20260518150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Priest  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends when a mobster is accused of murdering a priest. It doesn't take long before Matlock suspects that the Church is covering something up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518150000 +0000" stop="20260518160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Jinn Who Clears The Way</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Wo Fat is suspected of being behind the theft of a mobile ICBM device, and McGarrett with other top officials must stop him selling it off to the highest bidder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518160000 +0000" stop="20260518170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Vigil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Grandma is sick and Mary Ellen misdiagnosis the ailment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518170000 +0000" stop="20260518180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Money Store</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When he is refused a loan by the bank, Ray Jarvis' children find a way to steal the money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518180000 +0000" stop="20260518190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam and Laura are finally engaged. Adam is secretly building a house and planning for the future. However, Laura realizes that it's Will she is in love with. But when Adam is confined to a wheelchair after suffering a fall, Laura and Will deny their feelings out of guilt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518190000 +0000" stop="20260518193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Trail Of Hate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is out for vengeance when Mark is used as a pawn in a bank robbery scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518193000 +0000" stop="20260518200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Woman From Hog Ridge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas shoots a horse thief who turns out to be a member of the Boyle clan, and now Ma Boyle is after him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518200000 +0000" stop="20260518210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Joshua Gilliam Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill and the Major find a man lying hurt, and bring him into the wagon train. When he meets an innocent woman in the group who has an inheritance waiting for her, he shows other skills besides being just a schoolteacher—and her mother is wary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518210000 +0000" stop="20260518220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Virus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A sick lady with a monkey provides the key to a mysterious, highly contagious and deadly virus that strikes both Dr. Brackett and John. Meanwhile, the firemen rescue a boy from a treehouse and a man from a scaffold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518220000 +0000" stop="20260518223000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gestapo Takeover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo takes over Stalag 13, planning to send Klink and Schultz to the Russian Front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518223000 +0000" stop="20260518230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The General's Practitioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of Hawkeye being considered, much to his distaste, for the position of a general's personal physician, Radar becomes a surrogate father to a Korean woman and her baby, until the baby's GI father returns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518230000 +0000" stop="20260518233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Movie Tonight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a cure for the increased tension at the 4077th, Potter obtains a copy of his favorite film, "My Darling Clementine," and makes a social event out of it. As the film continues to break, tensions rise, until Mulcahy plays the piano, Radar does his impersonations and everyone acts out scenes from the film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260518233000 +0000" stop="20260519000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Souvenirs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Korean children and American soldiers are often badly wounded when they hunt for souvenirs that the enemy have booby-trapped. Potter asks for it to stop, and Hawkeye and B.J. put a local junk dealer out of business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519000000 +0000" stop="20260519003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee The Warden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Mayberry jail is filled to capacity with a group of moonshiners who blame Otis for their capture, Andy takes Otis home to serve his term.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519003000 +0000" stop="20260519010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Medicine Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, saddened by the death of a friend, is feeling old and tired. She stumbles across a medicine man's presentation and is intrigued by his bottle of elixir, which she believes to add pep to her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519010000 +0000" stop="20260519013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Somebody Hates Raymond</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray appears as a guest on a local sports radio show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519013000 +0000" stop="20260519020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Just A Formality</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert and Ray meet Amy's ultra-conservative parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519020000 +0000" stop="20260519023000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Zborn Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Dorothy finds herself being wooed by Stan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519023000 +0000" stop="20260519030000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>How Do You Solve A Problem Like Sophia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Sophia returns from the funeral of her best friend, Sister Agnes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519030000 +0000" stop="20260519033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway, Joan Rivers, And Vincent Price</sub-title>
    <desc>In Workshop with Willie, Tim plays a TV handyman surrounded by incompetent helpers. Then, in The Old Folks, Harvey wants to go to an adult film, and Carol responds with "I'm Old Fashioned". Finally, Carol and the gang perform classic TV parodies, including Police Lady, Chiquita and the Man, Rhonda, Tony Tallahassee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519033000 +0000" stop="20260519043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Blind Man's Bluff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Crooked jewelry store owner Karl Addison learns that he needs an operation that will temporarily blind him. Addison makes plans to rob his own store knowing that his sightlessness will provide him with a perfect alibi.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519043500 +0000" stop="20260519050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Long Live Walter Jameson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A history teacher talks about the past as if he had lived it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519050500 +0000" stop="20260519053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Post Mortem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman learns that a winning sweepstakes ticket is in the suit her husband was buried in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519053500 +0000" stop="20260519060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Crocodile Case</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A man murders his lover's husband to have her for himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519060500 +0000" stop="20260519070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Moving Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is convinced that the man who is intending to kill Ken Mitchell is his own partner, Paul Anders. Yet the whole thing becomes muddled when Ken confesses that Anders is a fictitious character he came up with only for tax purposes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519070500 +0000" stop="20260519080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Devil's Playground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A former motorcycle officer who was disabled when a thief tried to steal the payroll from an armored car, seeks Frank's help for the purpose of exacting his revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519080500 +0000" stop="20260519090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Temptation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>As a police lieutenant ends up falling for the ex-girlfriend of a murderer in trying to make her a witness to have the murderer convicted, he's framed for the murder of a second witness, so Barnaby and J.R. try to clear him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519090000 +0000" stop="20260519093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>S.i.u. - The Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon recruit a woman cop to nab a burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519093000 +0000" stop="20260519100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Medical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate cases in a hospital emergency ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519100000 +0000" stop="20260519103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 15 -- Exactly One Hundred Yards</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>On their day off, Malloy and Reed agree to give a talk to a group of fifth grade students, and then offer to let the kids watch them train for the California Police Olympics. But when the tires of their patrol car are slashed and a stopwatch goes missing out of reed's car, the two officers start to suspect one of the children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519103000 +0000" stop="20260519110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 153 -- Find Me A Needle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for the "Mulholland Mauler," who has raped six female hitchhikers and left them for dead. They quickly make an arrest of a likely suspect and take him to the location of an abandoned vehicle, after learning its owner never made it to her destination.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519110000 +0000" stop="20260519120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Back In '96!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony revisit the year 1996."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519120000 +0000" stop="20260519123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's I.q.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>After learning that he's going to be taking an I.Q. test, Beaver hits the books, scared after his friends tell him that if he doesn't pass he will be sent to "dumb school."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519123000 +0000" stop="20260519130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Goes In Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Gilbert begin a lawn mowing business and plan to go door to door in seach of lawns that need to be mowed. However, shortly after they venture out, Eddie gives the boys some advice that leads them into trouble and Gilbert to bail out of the business when their first client appears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519130000 +0000" stop="20260519140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Drifting Dropout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason defends a mixed-up man accused of killing his former boss. The young man's uncle had been a business partner of the deceased and was quite a crook. Scandal and intrigue run deep and it's up to Mason to dredge up the culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519140000 +0000" stop="20260519150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Court Martial: Part 1  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock is hired by a friend to defend his enlisted son. The boy's been charged with killing a sadistic lieutenant whose mistreatment led to the death of another soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519150000 +0000" stop="20260519160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Fools Die Twice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Army computer technician Jack Gulley kidnaps a scientist and then uses a planned heist by three accomplices on a military base to divert Five-O's attention from his sale of the scientist to the highest bidder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519160000 +0000" stop="20260519170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Comeback</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason's scholarship at the music academy is canceled</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519170000 +0000" stop="20260519180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Twisted Heritage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Kitty saves the life of a man during a stage hold-up. Taking him back to his ranch, she finds his mother a ruthless matron and his daughter alienated from her father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519180000 +0000" stop="20260519190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Walter And The Outlaws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss agrees to dog-sit Obie's dog, Walter, while he is away. What Hoss doesn't anticipate is a confrontation with outlaws that turns a simple task into a comic chain of events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519190000 +0000" stop="20260519193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Seven</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Seven condemned murderers escape and take over the town of North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519193000 +0000" stop="20260519200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Pitchman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mark finds gold on their property, a fast-talking salesman who tried to sell Lucas a new lightning rod offers instead to buy the ranch's mineral rights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519200000 +0000" stop="20260519210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Maggie Hamilton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>When their daughter runs away from the wagon train, the Hamiltons hire Flint to bring her back. With renegades in the area, he soon discovers how spoiled Maggie really is, but they still manage to make it back in one piece.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519210000 +0000" stop="20260519220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Peace Pipe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A drunk driver rams a parked car, trapping a child inside. Chet pesters John about his Native American heritage. A kid gets his finger stuck in a gumball machine. A woman's new girdle causes breathing difficulties. A worker's error leads to fuel being mixed with the water supply, causing explosive results. A sniper makes a scaffold rescue dangerous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519220000 +0000" stop="20260519223000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Kommandant Schultz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Schultz lets his new power as camp kommandant go to his head.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519223000 +0000" stop="20260519230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Post Op</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of a deluge of patients and their individual medical histories, the 4077th is out of blood. Everyone in camp is donating at 48-hour intervals when a truckload of Turkish soldiers arrives to offer their blood and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519230000 +0000" stop="20260519233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Margaret's Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Prompted by pressure from Frank, Hot Lips sets a date for marriage with Lieutenant Colonel Donald Penobscott. When Donald arrives in camp for the wedding, a bridal shower and bachelor party are given. When he has passed out drunk, Hawkeye and B.J. place Donald in a body cast and convince him that he has broken his leg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260519233000 +0000" stop="20260520000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520000000 +0000" stop="20260520003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three Wishes For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney acquires some fortune-telling cards and a secret box. The cards promise magical occurrences, and when his wish is granted, he becomes convinced that the box has mystical powers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520003000 +0000" stop="20260520010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer The House Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy takes Gomer in after Wally fires him for not doing his job right. Gomer proceeds to drive Andy, Aunt Bee and Opie crazy with all of the noise he makes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520010000 +0000" stop="20260520013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Disciplinarian, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra convinces Ray that it's his turn to discipline the kids.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520013000 +0000" stop="20260520020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Sweet Charity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray starts spending less time at home when he volunteers at a hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520020000 +0000" stop="20260520023000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. George Devereaux</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Blanche has a secret admirer and is shocked when she meets him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520023000 +0000" stop="20260520030000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Girls Just Wanna Have Fun Before They Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Both Sophia and Rose take advice from Blanche.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520030000 +0000" stop="20260520033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests William Conrad And Alan King</sub-title>
    <desc>In Laurel and Hardy, the gang pays homage to the slapstick duo. Then, in The Other Doctor, Harvey and Bill are golfing pals until a rival doctor comes between them. Finally, Carol and the gang perform a classic TV commercial parody on kitchen products.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520033000 +0000" stop="20260520043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Barefaced Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In a small California town throwing a festival during which all men wear beards, Paul Drake tries to locate missing money embezzled by a former bank president.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520043500 +0000" stop="20260520050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>People Are Alike All Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>When a space exploration crashes on Mars, the surviving passenger is surprised to find that Martians are human-looking, very friendly and apparently just like us.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520050500 +0000" stop="20260520053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Profit-sharing Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's plan to run away with his company's funds encounters a small hitch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520053500 +0000" stop="20260520060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Safe Place</sub-title>
    <desc>"A bank teller schemes the perfect plan."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520060500 +0000" stop="20260520070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Cry Pigeon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A power struggle between two crime lords may erupt into war with Mannix standing in the middle. After arranging a secret reunion between the lords, the son of one of them is shot to death and Mannix is blamed for the ambush.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520070500 +0000" stop="20260520080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Treasure Of San Ignacio</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Stolen precious artifacts from a church in Mexico, has Cannon in search of three suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520080500 +0000" stop="20260520090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Man On Fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby works with a claims adjuster in an arson-and-murder case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520090000 +0000" stop="20260520093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Mister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The police zero in on a rat: a forger, bigamist and thief who even robs from the blind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520093000 +0000" stop="20260520100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Little Pusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates the junior high drug scene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520100000 +0000" stop="20260520103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 52 -- Good Cop: Handle With Care</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed see a man passed out in an alley and stop to lend assistance, deliver bad news to a young wife, apprehend a mentally ill man who then becomes uncontrollably violent in their patrol car, and respond to a robbery that needlessly becomes a tragedy. All along the way the officers have their every move second guessed by a pair of young, unethical freelance journalists who are determined to document police brutality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520103000 +0000" stop="20260520110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 23: Pig Is A Three Letter Word</sub-title>
    <desc>"The officers are subjected to verbal abuse when they arrest armed robbers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520110000 +0000" stop="20260520120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>An Acme Company History</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony discover Acme inspired products."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520120000 +0000" stop="20260520123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Glamour Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is shocked to learn that the glamorous Kitty Bannerman is visiting Mayfield and he's afraid that she will find out that he's not the rich hot shot that he told her he was in the letters that he had sent her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520123000 +0000" stop="20260520130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Double Cross</sub-title>
    <desc>"Eddie crawls through the Cleaver house spreading the news that he's going steady with Caroline Schuster, something that worries June who doesn't want Wally to get any ideas about going steady. However, Wally has other worries when he overhears Caroline saying that she's only using Eddie while her boyfriend is grounded. Leaving Wally with the decision to tell Eddie or not."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520130000 +0000" stop="20260520140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Tandem Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E29</episode-num>
    <desc>After a hated businessman is killed in a sabotaged automobile, his future son-in-law—who the businessman despised—is arrested for the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520140000 +0000" stop="20260520150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Court Martial: Part 2  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>As the murder case involving the death of a sadistic Army lieutenant progresses, Matlock discovers that the lieutenant and four other officers may have been involved in smuggling drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520150000 +0000" stop="20260520160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Chain Of Events</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520160000 +0000" stop="20260520170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Baptism</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous evangelist visits Walton's Mountain to preach and baptize converts</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520170000 +0000" stop="20260520180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Time Of The Jackals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A former girlfriend of Matt's provides a link to catch a notorious killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520180000 +0000" stop="20260520190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Invention Of A Gunfighter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe teaches Johnny Chapman how to use a gun for defense. What Joe doesn't see is the deadly consequences that it has in the long run when Johnny becomes a gunfighter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520190000 +0000" stop="20260520193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Strange Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Micah is badly injured by an escaping prisoner, Lucas tracks the prisoner back to his home town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520193000 +0000" stop="20260520200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Baranca</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When an outlaw leader lures Marshal Torrance out of town, Lucas is the only one who can stop him from lynching a local man who killed one of the members of his gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520200000 +0000" stop="20260520210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jonas Murdock Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Out of meat and low on food, the wagon train must not kill any wildlife or all will face the wrath of local indians. The one holdout is Jonas Murdoch, who has always lived outside the rules and doesn't consider a rabbit an issue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520210000 +0000" stop="20260520220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Saddled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Dixie injures her toe. John decides he can make a lot of money by riding in rodeos. The squad goes to a hole-in-the-wall restaurant when a soda bottle explodes in a girl's face; later, they return for a gas explosion. After falling from a tree, a young boy lapses into a coma. The firemen rescue several children and a nun from a bus crash.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520220000 +0000" stop="20260520223000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Eight O'clock And All Is Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan finds that a new prisoner is a German spy right after he tells the man all about their secret operations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520223000 +0000" stop="20260520230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520230000 +0000" stop="20260520233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fallen Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar wants to become a man so Hawkeye recommends he goes to Seoul. On his way there he is hit by a mine. Hawkeye performs surgery on him. After surgery, Hawkeye goes to the Officers Club where he gets hammered. The next day he goes to surgery severely hung over. Radar tells Hawkeye he is disappointed in him. Hawkeye explodes and is then yelled at by Major Houlihan, Colonel Potter and Father Mulcahy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260520233000 +0000" stop="20260521000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Last Laugh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Madness strikes as B.J. and his old friend, Bardonaro, play a series of practical jokes on each other, just as Bardonaro is about to leave Korea. Hawkeye gets the last laugh. He sends Bardonaro off without his traveling papers, and in a jeep with too little gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521000000 +0000" stop="20260521003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober And The Art Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney try to set the perpetually unlucky-in-love Goober up with a woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521003000 +0000" stop="20260521010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Floyd The Gay Deceiver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Madeline Grayson, a rich widow that Floyd has been "pen-palling" with, announces in her next letter that she wants to meet him face-to-face. Of course, the whole time Floyd has been pretending in his letters to be a wealthy entrepreneur.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521010000 +0000" stop="20260521013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Meeting The Parents</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Amy's parents arrive unexpectedly at her apartment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521013000 +0000" stop="20260521020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Plan, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert is put in charge of selecting his wedding invitations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521020000 +0000" stop="20260521023000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Stand By Your Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Blanche meets a man at the library.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521023000 +0000" stop="20260521030000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Ebbtide's Revenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Dorothy must give the eulogy at her brother Phil's funeral.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521030000 +0000" stop="20260521033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Boxerette, Carol boxes with Tim, who's refuses to hit a girl. Then, in The Oldest Man, officer Harvey interviews Tim, the Oldest Man, about a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521033000 +0000" stop="20260521043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Difficult Detour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Contactor Pete Mallory is charged with the murder of a vacation resort developer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521043500 +0000" stop="20260521050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Execution</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Just before being hanged for murder, a man in 1880 is transported to the future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521050500 +0000" stop="20260521053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Canary Sedan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E37</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman hears voices in her car when she arrives in Hong Kong to join her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521053500 +0000" stop="20260521060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Impromptu Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A lawyer decides to murder one of his clients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521060500 +0000" stop="20260521070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Walk In The Shadows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Tom Farnon is in a tight spot: When he wants to catch his wife, Linda, with her lover on his yacht, a shot rings out and Linda falls dead overboard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521070500 +0000" stop="20260521080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Blood On The Vine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A doctor who is conducting a medical research project at the state prison is the victim of harassment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521080500 +0000" stop="20260521090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In Hawaii (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In Hawaii, J.R. is framed for murder and thrown in jail by a vengeful cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521090000 +0000" stop="20260521093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Cigarette Butt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A murder victim's smoking habits help Friday track down the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521093000 +0000" stop="20260521100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Missing Person</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A high school student is missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521100000 +0000" stop="20260521103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 83 -- A Different Thing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An older husband complains about his wife and friend's noisy karate practice. A hit and run traffic accident looks looks like a homicide. The officers use their investigative skills to locate the suspect and arrest him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521103000 +0000" stop="20260521110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 103 -- A Sound Like Thunder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and his date join Reed and his expecting wife on a weekend trip to a ghost town, but soon they cross paths with a dangerous motorcycle gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521110000 +0000" stop="20260521120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill Gets Glasses</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill reveals a new look with glasses."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521120000 +0000" stop="20260521123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Lander's Fiancee</sub-title>
    <desc>"While doing some yard work for Miss Landers, Beaver and Whitey witness their favorite teacher in the midst of a gentleman caller, which makes Beaver a bit jealous. However, Beaver gets sick to his stomach when he discovers Miss Landers is engaged to be married and the man he saw was her fiance."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521123000 +0000" stop="20260521130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Chuckie's New Shoes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A neighbor gives Wally the responsibility of taking her son, Chuckie, down to the shoe store to pick out a pair of shoes. However, when Wally gives the job to Beaver, Beaver finds himself searching for Chuckie, who has gotten himself lost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521130000 +0000" stop="20260521140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ugly Duckling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A prospective heiress to a toy company must soon marry if she wishes to inherit her father's business. When it surfaces that her new boyfriend is being paid to romance her by her uncle, murder is not far behind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521140000 +0000" stop="20260521150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Good Boy  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Hating his mother's new boyfriend, Tony Morgen kills the man and frames his mother. Matlock takes the case to prove the woman's innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521150000 +0000" stop="20260521160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Journey Out Of Limbo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Danno is found in the back of a truck, dazed and confused, and McGarrett and the others must help him piece together how he came to be in that situation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521160000 +0000" stop="20260521170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Firestorm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>John Boy publishes excerpts from Hitler's writing in his newspaper and the town is upset.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521170000 +0000" stop="20260521180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Mannon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After shooting Festus and taking his mule, gunman Will Mannon comes to Dodge to face Matt in a gunfight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521180000 +0000" stop="20260521190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaws capture Ben and hide him in an abandoned mine, holding him for a ransom. The boys must come up with a plan to save him before it's too late.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521190000 +0000" stop="20260521193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Martinet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A former army captain comes to North Fork to kill the man who shot down his son in a gunfight—Lucas McCain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521193000 +0000" stop="20260521200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Milly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A new store owner upsets the town by demanding that all credit accounts be paid off.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521200000 +0000" stop="20260521210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Amos Gibbon Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>After an argument with Major Adams, Flint leaves the wagon train and cozies up to a bar at a nearby town. What he doesn't know is the locals are shanghaiing strangers for slave labor in a mine and no one on the train knows where he went.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521210000 +0000" stop="20260521220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Fuzz Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>John falls for a lady deputy when called to treat a mugger. Items are stolen from Rampart. The firemen rescue an elderly man from a house fire. Boot returns to Station 51. A grandfather is injured by a model rocket. The paramedics rescue a boat thief trapped on a crane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521220000 +0000" stop="20260521223000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Watch The Trains Go By</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan arranges for Burkhalter's sister to keep Klink occupied, so he can leave camp and blow up a train.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521223000 +0000" stop="20260521230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Of Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th, caught up in tension and nerves, creates a bonfire to release their pressure. Meanwhile, Sidney Freedman is depressed over a young soldier who blames him for his injuries, because Freedman had sent him back into combat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521230000 +0000" stop="20260521233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Winchester Tapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tries unsuccessfully to get to Seoul, to see Nurse Gilmore for the weekend. Meanwhile, Winchester has taped a letter home, asking for his influential parents to help get him back to the States. To get even, Hawkeye and B.J. switch Winchester's clothes, causing Winchester to alter his eating patterns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260521233000 +0000" stop="20260522000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Light That Failed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>With supplies low, the 4077th gets a truckload of ice cream churns and salt tablets. But what it needs are light bulbs, and in the dimly lit post-op Charles makes an error for which he draws the ultimate wrath of his two surgeon bunkmates. Meanwhile, B.J. receives a mystery novel that everyone in camp reads in turn. The last page is missing and the solution to the mystery is undiscovered until B.J. calls the author by long distance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522000000 +0000" stop="20260522003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>My Fair Ernest T. Bass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy tries to make a silk purse out of a sow's ear when he takes it upon himself to turn Ernest T. into a presentable gentleman. The big test comes at Mrs. Wiley's weekly reception, at which Andy passes him off as his cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522003000 +0000" stop="20260522010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Otis has Mayberry worried when he buys a car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522010000 +0000" stop="20260522013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Sleepover At Peggy's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond is horrified when he thinks his "cookie nemesis" flirted with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522013000 +0000" stop="20260522020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Who's Next?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray seems pleased when Debra picks an attractive friend to replace her if she dies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522020000 +0000" stop="20260522023000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Bloom Is Off The Rose, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Rose wants more adventure in her relationship with Miles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522023000 +0000" stop="20260522030000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Sisters Of The Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Blanche's gay brother Clayton, makes a visit to Miami with a surprise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522030000 +0000" stop="20260522033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Bernadette Peters</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Stickups, three criminals accidently rob the same bar at the same time. Then, in The Old Folks, Harvey applies to be a guard at the bank. Next, in The Typists, Carol and her co-workers live their lives in beat with their typewriters. Finally, in Movie Pantomime, Carol finds a friend at the movies, only he's disgusted with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522033000 +0000" stop="20260522043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Cowardly Lion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hilde Fursten and Tony Osgood work at the San Diego Zoo. When a baby monkey goes missing, Fursten is blamed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522043500 +0000" stop="20260522050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Tall Wish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A boy who believes in magic thinks he is helping a boxer win with his "big, tall wish."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522050500 +0000" stop="20260522053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Little White Frock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E39</episode-num>
    <desc>A producer is surprised when an actor announces his retirement plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522053500 +0000" stop="20260522060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Apex</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A man and his lover decide to get rid of his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522060500 +0000" stop="20260522070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Only One Death To A Customer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After escaping three consecutive attempts on his life, Mannix learns that someone has placed a $5,000 bounty on his head.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522070500 +0000" stop="20260522080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>To Kill A Guinea Pig</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon discovers that a man is posing as the son of a wine maker is likely the suspect of the three death attempts already tried against his "father."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522080500 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In Hawaii (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In Hawaii, J.R. is framed for murder and thrown in jail by a vengeful cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The policeman's role in court is highlighted in this episode.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
